The reason why I'm here
is that I'll protect you
Don't worry, let's go ahead and go ahead
All right Cape should be here any
second now let's go robin you'll
have to get on that train sooner
later you heard me take the lady and
get moving you dimwits yes sir a
government rep a bunch of marines and
robin let's see how should i play
this because inside of me i carry a
darkness that none of you know about
no matter how you look at it they're
obviously escorting her away but
those guys are chumps if she wanted
to run she could take them out no
problem she must be planning something
we don't know about there's got to
be a reason why she's not running?
Oh, you want me to save you, Robin?
Corgi, sir!
Cape is here!
Stop handling me down!
Oh, man!
That's Rob Lucci, huh?
Huh?
He's got the eyes of a killer.
Never thought I'd see CP9 in person.
I'm gonna give you to the cabin tank.
And then it's gonna get
ugly. You hear me? Let me go!
You don't know who you're messing with.
I got 8,000 men hiding in the shadows
just waiting to teach you losers a lesson.
Yeah, they're gonna
pop out any minute now.
Any minute, you hear me?
Better put it out!
Who's up to?
excellent work as always sirs and madam
here mr.
Lead coat what is this a parade stop
it it's foolish ah right sorry sir
This isn't over until
we reach Enies Lobby so
look sharp everyone board
the c-train immediately.
You heard the man get
on the train and make
it quick hey you bastards
gonna put me down?
Who are those guys in the suits?
He says he's sorry for
causing us so much trouble
then he goes and gets in
trouble all over again.
A little further to the right!
Spray over there!
Bring the hose this way!
So, you mean Robin
doesn't hate us after all?
Uh-huh!
I'm so happy!
Huh?
He's a raccoon dog?
I thought he was a reindeer.
Did he just transform or what?
Anyway, Chopper,
we have to find the rest of the crew
right away so we can go rescue Robin.
Okay, let's go!
Uh, but where are they?
I don't know.
That's why we have to find them.
Yeah!
That's new day!
Whoa!
Now he's a gorilla!
Wait, you two.
Huh?
I don't care if you go after Nico Robin,
but before you run off,
you should know that the
C-Train for Government
Personnel is departing
at 11 o 'clock tonight.
This is just my guess, but there's
a good chance you'll find CP9 there.
and that means Nico Robin
will be there as well.
Thanks to Aqua Laguna, they're
stopping all service after this final?
departure.
In other words, you won't be
able to chase him on another
train.
Wait, you mean we have to...
Since you obviously can't
sail in this weather,
you won't be able to leave the island
unless you go after that train right now.
Huh? No way!
What time is it?
Almost 10.30. What?
That means we've only
got half an hour left!
Hey, you're the mayor, right?
Can't you do something to stop the train?
Well, unfortunately, it's
bound for Eni's lobby,
which is only accessible
to government personnel.
Even the engine driver works for the
government, so I have no say in this matter.
Oh, no.
I guess our only choice is to head to the
station and try to talk
some sense into Robin.
Chopper? Huh?
I'll tell you which direction
Luffy and Zoro flew off in,
so you go search there, okay?
If you find them, tell them to come
to the station as quickly as they can.
Okay, got it.
Hey, listen up.
Oh, look, you guys. Polly's okay.
See that girl over there?
I want you to help her find her buddies.
You sure that smoke didn't
get in your brain, Polly?
These are the guys that tried to kill Mr.
Iceberg.
We should ring their Newgate sorry necks.
Besides, why should we waste our time?
Helping some criminals?
when Luchi and Kaku are still missing?
The Straw Hats aren't the
ones who did it, okay?
The real criminals set them up.
If we hadn't been so damn blind, we
wouldn't be in this situation right now.
I don't know the real identity
of those guys in the masks,
but I do know that the Straw Hats
tried to protect us from them.
As a matter of fact,
Iceberg and I wouldn't even be alive
right now if it wasn't for their help.
Don't bother looking for Luchi and Kaku.
There's no point.
In fact, I don't know if we'll
ever be seeing them again.
What?
If you know what happened to the
foreman, then you gotta tell us, Paulie.
They went back home. Huh?
Why would they do that
at a time like this?
Just shut up and go find Straw Hat.
Hey, immoral girl.
What?
You're still calling me that?
If you're going to the
station, I'll show you the way.
Uh, thanks, I guess.
Hey, hold on a sec, Paulie.
Is that stuff you told us true?
Quit your yapping and
help them out already.
You're making Galley-La look bad.
Yes! Sorry, sir!
We'll do our best!
You're the boss!
Yeah!
We'll help any way we can!
Open the cage!
Bring out the Yagadas!
Yeah!
Went back home, did they?
I spared them the details.
It's better that way.
It was bad enough when we found out.
They deserved the truth?
but I don't want to hurt those guys.
Hey! Guys! Hello!
Hey, guys!
Can you hear me?
Help me!
Zoro! Sanji!
Osop, you can come with us too, okay?
Now share it with me!
All right, buddy, you got it!
Let's do it, guys!
Hey!
Luffy!
The road!
Again!
Issie, you can come with us, too!
Take that canal over
on the left-hand side!
It's a shortcut to the station!
we still have 20 minutes before
the train leaves don't go
Robin you don't have to sacrifice
yourself we can save you mr.
Yagra you think you can go
a little bit faster please
the 11 o 'clock train
is about to depart all
passengers going from from
Blue Station to Eni's lobby.
Please board immediately.
That hurts!
I don't want to hear
another word out of you two.
Well, maybe I wouldn't complain so
much if you weren't such big jerkwads!
Yeah, you big jerkwads!
Why don't you come over here and fight?
Hey, that's too much.
Due to the approaching storm surge,
the departure time has been moved up?
and the train will be departing shortly.
Damn it.
This was bad enough already.
After all these years, our mission
has finally come to an end.
We're not there yet.
Stop spouting nonsense and take
your mission seriously, you fool.
My apologies.
You can't sail in this weather.
Unless you can catch that train,
you won't be able to leave. Come on!
We're so close!
Franky, wherever you
are, I hope you're safe.
Hey, Lupin!
Row, row, go on! Lupin! Hey!
Come back!
Where are you?
Come on, there's not much time!
Zoro! Sanji!
Usa, you can come too.
Luffy!
Please, those guys are
gonna take Robin away!
We need your help!
Where are you?
I wonder how the rest of the
crew is dealing with this mess.
Anyway, time's up.
They'll have to catch me later.
I repeat, the final train will
be departing ahead of schedule.
Please board immediately.
Gentlemen!
You bastards!
I'm coming for you! Just wait! You'll see!
Let me get out of here!
One little slip-up,
then this crap happens.
I'm coming for you bastards.
Once I get out of here...
Help me!
No help! Sergeant!
Where are you?
We've got a safe roomie!
STRAWHAAAA!
RORO NOA!
I don't get it.
Where in the heck are they?
Have we checked over there yet?
Hey!
STRAWHAAAA! ZORO!
I guess they're not here.
Has anybody checked over
in the back streets yet?
I don't know if we can.
They're probably
completely flooded by now.
It'd be too dangerous
to look for them there.
Come on, guys!
Where are you?
There's no time!
Excuse me.
The waves are getting dangerously high,
so we've decided to depart
early as a safety measure.
If there's any trouble, we could...
It's fine. Just go. Yahoo!
Yeah.
Yes, sir.
We lived here for five years.
But even as we leave, I don't
feel nostalgic in the least?
Hey, was that a steam whistle just now?
If it was, that means
the train is running.
Nearly 15 minutes ahead of schedule,
they're probably taking off early
because the weather's getting bad.
The government runs that line so
they can leave whenever they want.
Hurry it up, guys.
The station's right there.
Hold on, train don't leave yet.
Me, me.
Attention.
Tonight's final departure?
heading from Water 7 to Eni's
lobby is now leaving the station.
You heard her.
Sit down already.
Have a safe trip.
I wanted nothing more than
to die at that very moment.
But you forced me to live.
That's your crime.
I'm afraid there's no place
left for me to go or return to.
So I've decided to stay here with you!
I see your problem?
Guess there's no other choice, is there?
Welcome You're afraid?
Hey, there's nothing to worry about
She isn't a bad person, trust me, okay?
Hey, I think we're moving.
Stupid government jerkwats!
Good job, Mr. Yagura!
Go down the stairs, through
the middle entrance!
Got it!
We're coming for you, Robin!
Please don't go!
Hey, stop! Who are you?
That's dangerous! Stay back!
Robin, get off that train!
I don't care who you're up
against, we'll help you!
Luffy!
Solo!
Where are you guys?
Cat-Wolf.
Wait!
No!
Come back!
Robin!
Looks like we were too late.
Ow!
Seriously, what was that
guy trying to pull anyway?
Whatever the case, it
really doesn't matter.
That was a government train.
It'll be captured, and
that will be the end of it.
Hey, isn't he with Galley-La?
Hey, Paul!
Try to act professional, will you?
It looks like there's something
going on between them.
This is a train station.
People say hello and
goodbye here every day.
It's our responsibility as employees here
to silently oversee things like this.
Yeah, you're right.
Keep quiet, got it?
Train left a little early, huh?
Yes, that's right.
All of the passengers were already
on board, so they decided...
The weather's getting
rougher by the minute, too.
At this rate, Aqua Laguna
could hit at any moment.
With all of these factors in mind,
it was decided that departure
time should be pushed
forward it's not safe here
right now you should take
shelter on the shipbuilding
island as soon as possible
yeah you're right hey listen
the trains gone there's
nothing we can do to stop it
I hate to say it but any's
lobby isn't the kind of place
where are you crying hey
look I I understand how you
must feel after them she's
passed i'll never forgive
those world government idiots
listen i need a ship what in
the hell are you talking about
the strongest and fastest
you've got you want to set sail
in the middle of all this don't
be an idiot do you have any
idea how dangerous this storm
is lay off i can handle it look
this isn't some regular
run-of-the-mill storm we're
talking about it's about to be
hell at sea around here it's
impossible to Now doing so is
nothing short of a death wish
listen to me Robin is throwing
her life away for our sake and I'm
that was close
thank you yes thank
you you saved us all if
it wasn't for you we
would have all been swept
out into the sea look at
that that huge fixture
with the train schedule
on it was torn apart
nothing like that has ever happened
here before not even with aqua laguna
This thing's power is unbelievable
And the actual storm isn't even here
yet Aqua Laguna is different this
year These waves are coming in fast
Hey, is that Sea Train that they
took Robin on in any danger?
It should be able to make
it out of this rough patch.
Before the actual storm makes landfall?
Unless it takes a direct hit!
That train's capable of cutting
through these big waves.
Um, excuse me, are you Nami? Huh? Yes?
Someone left you a note out
in front of the station.
Must have been one of your crewmates!
A note? From who?
And how did you manage to
notice something so small?
It was right here!
Whoever it was made it easy for us!
That dimwit
So what does it say?
Give me a second.
The first half is just
a hopeless love letter.
Did she say love letter?
It seems there's a love
triangle going on here.
No.
Considering the situation, I'd
say the other man is most likely.
What are you staring at?
The important part starts here.
P .S.
I saw Robin get on the 11 o 'clock train.
I'm going to hop on board and follow her.
Sanji got on board that train?
Usopp's there too?
And some arrogant thug with
a duck tail. Who's that?
That must be Franky.
Yeah, must be.
She mentioned another man,
and it sounds like Franky of
all people must be the fifth.
Poor Polly doesn't stand a chance.
Maybe it'd be better if he
just threw in the towel.
What in the hell is with you guys?
Oh, and there's something else.
This was left on the ground
alongside that letter.
There should be at least one transponder
snail somewhere on that C-train.
I'll contact you as soon as I can.
Keep this portable one close to
you at all times, my darling.
Just pretend it's me and hold it lovingly
against your soft meat. I get it.
He left this one to
communicate with us. Wow.
He must have anticipated
Nico Robin's movements.
Pretty impressive. I'll say.
At least for the time being,
Robin has Sanji with her.
The rest of us will just have to
catch up with them at Innie's lobby.
Man, can't even manage to light
up a single smoke out here.
Really?
So after that, Sanji went
to the train station? Yep.
And Usopp's on the train
with him. Thank goodness.
At any rate,
no matter how we're going to follow them,
we can't do anything until we find
Luffy and Zoro first, understand?
Right.
I got it, Nami.
I'm 100 % certain about
which way they flew,
so head in that direction
and start looking.
You guys help look, too!
Let's do this!
Are you with me? Yeah!
We won't let you down!
Now, what would be the best way
for one to sneak inside this thing?
Whoa!
This storm is insane!
Huh?
Oh, yeah, shoot! Oh! Whoa!
Who in the hell are you?
AHHHHHH!
Hey, hold it.
Where do you think you're going?
Don't move!
Whoa, did you see that kick?
He's not some run-of-the-mill civilian.
Huh?
Come on now.
Well, if you keep saying things like that,
I'll blush.
It wasn't a compliment!
He's making fun of us.
Hey, go let Rob Lucci know that we've
got a suspicious intruder on board.
Wait a minute!
This insignificant little matter isn't
something we need to bother CP9 with.
No matter how violent or unruly this
man is, it won't do him any good.
Because in this car, you've got...
Whoa, it's smokey.
In this car, you've got me, Jerry.
That's right.
You're looking at the champion on a south
blue island renowned for his martial arts.
The undefeated boxing champion.
I prefer karate.
If you can handle my punches,
then maybe I'll show you some.
Easy, no need to overdo it! Jerry!
The girl!
Hey, Jerry, your target's behind you!
You're a sneaky one.
Now listen, don't think you
have me at a disadvantage.
Just because I'm so very tall and
this train car is so very tiny!
This is the first time I've ever talked to
someone whose head is where
their crotch should be.
My boxing technique is more
effective in tight places like this!
Prepare for annihilation!
Go yoga style! One, two!
You just shortened your reach!
That's what you think!
All part of the plan!
That's totally against
every single rule of boxing!
This is a waste of time.
Oh, shit!
I'll start with the seventh and last car.
All of the world government
officials are there.
In order of increasing
strength, the fifth car is next.
That car holds 40 marines
and the man who leads
them a navy headquarters
captain and former
knight named t-bone next in the fourth car
we have wanze an
accomplished martial artist
from Cipher pole number
seven who also happens
to be the head steward
on this trip standing
by in the third car is nero the newest
member of cp9 and a force to be reckoned with
anyway
although we are escorting
criminals with government
personnel as trained and
powerful as the ones i mentioned
we needn't worry about the
possibility of a raid our
military might is represented
throughout this train
Mr.
Foreman, it must be hard
for you to even move.
Maybe you should take a little break.
Don't be stupid.
This is nothing.
Hurry up and find them.
Yes, sir.
Has anyone gone to bring
Iceberg up to speed?
Two men went to give him a report.
Hey, where are you going, Mr.
Iceberg?
Sir?
Hey, Zoro!
Where are you?
Answer us, Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Zoro, Luffy!
Come on, guys, answer me!
Where the heck are you?
What's that?
Food, you say?
Yes, that's right.
We need meat.
All the meat you can find.
And hurry, we're running out of time.
How did we end up being a couple
of errand boys for that girl?
We're not doing this for her.
We're doing it for Paulie.
He's so devoted to that crazy
woman even after she dumped him.
We've got to give this our all.
Yeah, you're right.
Keep going.
In any case, she must be really hungry.
She's still a growing
girl, right? I guess.
Oh, rain.
This is bad.
The strong winds are already
interfering with my sense of smell.
Man, I'm beat.
It feels like we've been calling for
hours, but there's still no answer.
You think maybe they're...
Don't be ridiculous.
Just keep trying.
Luffy, Zoro, where in the world are you?
There's no way that
leopard guy took you out.
We finally know why Robin left us,
and we need to do something about it.
Straw Hat, where are you?
Answer us, please!
Hang in there, Robin.
Loopy and the rest of us are
coming to save you no matter what
What's going on here?
Oh, Paulie quick come see for yourself
No more the tide recedes the bigger
the returning waves will be if you pay
attention to the episode you can measure
the magnitude of the storm surge.
I'm flying!
And if you consider how much lower the
water level's going to be this year...
Hey, Chimney, take a look.
Whoa! Amazing!
It's almost as if the sea has dried up.
I haven't seen anything
like this in my entire life.
The power of the sea is astonishing.
No way.
How can the tide be so low?
I've never seen anything like it.
Just how big of a wave
is coming this time?
All of the back streets are going
to be completely swallowed up.
I hope nobody's still down there.
If there is, they'll die instantly.
The roar of the ocean.
It's gone.
Lock, Lock, Lock, Lock, Lock!
Hey, Granny!
Take a look over there!
I see something!
You do, do you? Yeah!
There's something between
those two buildings!
Come on, Granny! Look! Look!
Kokoro!
Oh!
If it isn't the pirate girl! Hey!
Miss Pirate Lady! Look! Look over there!
I see something!
Like what?
Just what are you going
on about, Jiminy? No way!
What happened to the sea?
It's dried up!
Luffy!
Hmm, that Straw Hat.
Isn't that your king of
the pirates, Captain?
Well?
That idiot!
Hey, hold on!
Where do you think you're going?
Don't go down there, it's dangerous!
Are you trying to kill yourself?
Awkwalakuna is gonna hit
at any moment! Come back!
The pirate girl went down the stairs!
What should we do?
Come back!
What if another wave hits?
You